Nighttime and Idols
Here we are at the end of an early one.
I would like to ask you all to tailor yourselves.
Yes, we are Crown Pop. We, Crown Pop, will be at Shinjuku Lenny on Sunday, April 23rd.
We are going to have a tiarang pop'n party season 1.
Yay!
It's a live show here, and we are composing a very nice live show that women can also enjoy,
We would love to have you all come. Please do.
I see. Will we see a different side of KRAP again?
Yes, I think so. We are discussing various things with the staff and deciding on the colors,
I don't want to spoil it.
I'd like to keep it a secret,
I think you will see a different side of Kulap than usual.
Can you at least give us a hint?
A hint?
You should definitely come to the event.
I'm quite outspoken,
You are a talker?
Yes, I am. So, what should I say?
It's all right.
Backstabbing,
Backstabbing?
Cute.
Cute backstop?
Yes, it's cute. It's more like a Crapo cute expression.
I see.
Something like that. Are you okay so far, Mr. Manager?
Yes, I think so.
So, it's cute. Enjoyable.
So it's a show that you definitely don't want to miss.
Yes, that's right. I hope you will come and enjoy it.
You can see the new Crapo at the concert,
Tomorrow's concert will be held.
That's right.
I think the women's tickets might be a little full when we record it,
There may be another one next time.
Yes, there will be.
Please check our website,
If you are interested, please come.
Is that all right with you?
If you are free on that day, you can definitely get in right away with a same-day ticket,
Please come.
Yesterday, there were no same-day tickets, but that's OK,
Well, well, there are still tickets available today, so please come.
Please come.
Honestly speaking. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
And,
And from September to December,
We will also be doing a hashtag Kurapokawaii nationwide spreading tour.
The tour will go all over Japan, from Hokkaido in the north to Okinawa in the south,
We will be touring all over Japan, from Hokkaido in the north to Okinawa in the south, so if you haven't seen Crapo live yet, we will be there to meet them,
We are looking forward to seeing you there,
Please look forward to it.
Also, on December 28th, Crown Pop will be doing a revenge live at ZEPP DIVERCITY,
Crown Pop will be performing at ZEPP DIVERCITY on December 28th as a revenge live show.
We released a video on YouTube earlier this year,
We hope to show you a more powerful performance over the next year,
I hope to show you a more powerful version of myself over the next year, so please look forward to it.
Now that that's settled, let me present you with a cup of energizing tea from Yagami.
I'm so glad.
Please take the tea.
Bon appétit.
It's delicious.
It's called Shirojoge Makinohara City tea, isn't it?
I love tea, and I've definitely had hot tea in the morning since I was in elementary school.
You have that side of you, too?
Yes, I do.
I have an active side.
I'm addicted to it, so I drink it all the time.
Is that so? Your fans already know that?
Ya-chan drinks tea every morning.
Yes, they know. Maybe they don't know.
It's true that this may be something you don't get a chance to talk about.
I'm glad I could show you a new side of me.
It's so delicious.
It was good. Thank you very much.
Now then, since the theme of this program is cute,
May I ask you to end on a cute note for the camera?
Yes, I will.
I'll go now.
Thank you for watching Kettle and Idol.
Please come back and see Lina again.
That's all for now, this is Lina from Crown Pop. Thank you.
I'm embarrassed.
Bye bye.
Yes. Thank you so much for watching, kettle and idols, everyone.
See you soon.